CURRICULUM VITAE WILKINS D. TOKPA

SUMMARY:

I am young, hardworking; highly motivated and blessed young man with excellent Information & Communications Technology as well as Computer Science and Applications knowledge with experience. This mentality drive me to be creative and humble to serve humanity.

PERSONAL INFORMATION:

Date of Birth : March 23, 1996

Place of Birth : Paynesville Montserrado county, Liberia

Nationality : Liberian

Phone : +91-805-058-0458/ +112016602105

Email : wilkinsdtokpa@gmail.com

Marital Status : Single

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND:

2021-Present : Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA) candidate,

Reva university, India 2024 Batch

2015-2016 High Schol Diploma, Green Pasture School System

Paynesville, Montserrado County Liberia

WORKING EXPERIENCE

2019-2020 : Data Entry/Secretary/Assist. Outreach Director

Building An Outstanding Society Academism

Paynesville, Peace Island Jacob Town

Montserrado County, Monrovia Liberia

Description:

- -Manage and provide update on record of the organization
- -Monitor (BOSA) Student's Progress with regards to scholarship and student Improvement.
- -Alert parents and institutions about upcoming event for (BOSA).
- -Manage the entire organization documents such as Diplomas, Certificates, upcoming Events, and Prepare The Spelling Bees Spelling List for All Institution Participating in the Program.

2018-2019 : Volunteer Instructor At (BOSA)

Wesley School System

St. Francis Junction, Jacob Town Paynesville, Monrovia Liberia

Description:

- -Working closely with students during (BOSA) Program.
- -Investigator of student's activities in class/on campus
- -Evaluator of effectiveness of students' activities in the class room
- -Moral Builder of student's behaviors

REFERENCES:

Mr. Alphonso A. Sesay

Founder & CEO at Building An Outstanding Society Academism

Paynesville peace Island Jacob Town

Contact: 0775- 559-559

Mr. Jefferson T. Yarbah Principal, Wesley School System Paynesville, St Francis Junction

Contact: 0777-546-464